Yes,
indeed.
It is called Lothric,
where the transitory lands of the Lords of Cinder converge.
Venturing north,
the pilgrims discover the truth of the Old Words,
the fire fades,
and the Lords go without rooms.
When the Link of Fire is threatened,
the bell tolls,
unearthing the Old Lords of Cinder from their graves.
The Old Lords say in top the deep.
Farron's undead Legion,
who are based swatches.
Then the recruited Lord of starters will box ofais' capital.
You're not a giant.
Only in truth,
the lords will abandon their thrills.
And the unkindled will rise.
The aimless,
accursed undead,
unfit,
even to be cinder.
And so it is...
the trash -seek of embers.